CURRICULUM VITAE

Mr. Panchal Dnyaneshwar Anantrao dnyaneshwarpanchal@gmail.com 9404060756

Objective

To work with a progressive institute in which I can contribute my skills and experience to enhance my own productivity at the same time achieving the institutional and student's objectives with the attribute of the time, quality and discipline.

| Qualification | | | | |
|-------------------|---|------------------------------------|---------------------|-----------|
| Degree | College/State | University /Board | Year | % |
| LLB | Dayanad Law College, Latur | S.R.T.M. University, Nanded | IV Sem. Appeared | |
| Ph.D. | Dayanand College of Arts, Latur (Research Centre) | S.R.T.M. University, Nanded | 17 July 2020 | Awarded |
| SET (English) | Maharashtra | Savitribai Phule Pune Uni. Pune | Jan 2016 | Qualified |
| NET(English) | UGC, New Delhi. | UGC, New Dehli | Nov 2014 | Qualified |
| NET(English) | UGC, New Delhi. | UGC, New Dehli | April 2014 | Qualified |
| SET(English) | Andhra Pradesh. | Osmania University Hydrabad | Nov 2013 | Qualified |
| M.Phil. (English) | S.L.L. S.R.T.M.U. Nanded | S.R.T.M.U. Nanded | 2016 | 6.4 % |
| B.Ed. | Govt. College of Education, Nanded. | S.R.T.M.U. Nanded | 2010 | 67.12% |
| M.A. (English) | Dayanand College of Arts, Latur. | S.R.T.M.U. Nanded | 2008 | 66.47% |
| B.A. | R.S. College, Latur. | S.R.T.M.U. Nanded | 2006 | 66.48% |
| HSC | R.S. College, Latur. | Latur Board | 2003 | 69.25% |
| S.S.C. | Deshikendra High School, Latur. | Latur Board | 2001 | 53.06% |

| Teaching Experience | | | |
|----------------------------|-------------|--------|-----------|
| Designation | Institution | Period | Basic Pay |

| Asst Prof in English | Smt. Sushiladevi Deshmukh Senior 2021-22 | | Clock Hour |
|----------------------|--|-------------------------------------|-----------------------------|
| Asst Froi in English | College, Latur. | 2021-22 | Basis |
| Asst Prof in English | GES's HPT Arts & RYK Science College, Nashik. | 2018-19 Full time Contract Basis | |
| Asst Prof in English | GES's HPT Arts & RYK Science College, Nashik. 2017-18 | | Full time CHB |
| Asst Prof in English | GES's Arts, Commerce and Science College, Jawhar, Dist-Palghar. | 2016-17 | Full time Contract Basis |
| Asst Prof in English | Smt. Sushiladevi Deshmukh Senior College, Latur. Clock Hou Basis | | Clock Hour Basis |
| Asst Prof in English | Dayanad College of Arts, Latur. | | Clock Hour Basis |

| Research Topics | |
|--------------------|--|
| Ph.D. | A Study of Amitav Ghosh's Selected Works in the Light of Ecocriticism |
| M.Phil. | Measure on the Problems in Teaching and learning English in Marathi medium High Schools: A Study of Selected Schools at Latur City. |

Research Publication

| Conference/Seminar/ webinar | Paper title | |
|--|--|--|
| International journal of Creative Research thoughts (IJCRT) | Gun Island: Not a Fiction but a Prediction | |
| New Man International Journal of Multimedia Studies (Published) | Population as Pollution in the Amitav Ghosh's novel The Hungry Tide | |
| New Man International Journal of Multimedia Studies (Published) | The Study of Ecocritical Perspectives in the novel The Hungry Tide | |
| National Seminar (Published) Nashik: Maharashtra | The Role of Artificial Intelligence in the English Language Classroom | |
| International Conference Tirucherapalli: Tamilnadu (Published) | The Application of Digital Age Multimedia Technology in the Teaching of Suprasegmental Features of English | |
| International Conference Nanded: Maharashtra (Published) | The Historical, Religious, Social Exhortation, Cultural and Identical Study of Powada as Folk Literature | |

Extra Curricular Activities

- NSS University Certificate.
- Participated in Youth Festival 2007 and 2010.

| Personal | | |
|---------------------|---|--|
| Information: | | |
| Date of Birth | 2 nd August 1986. | |
| Contact | 9404060756. | |
| Correspondence | F/304, Aasha kiran, Samarth Garden, datta mandir road, Bhandup (west) | |
| Address | 400078, Mumbai, Maharashtra | |
| Nationality | Indian. | |
| Languages | English, Hindi, Marathi. | |
| Known | | |
| Hobbies | Don't have any particular hobby but I like Trekking, Bike-riding, | |
| Strength | Honesty, Punctuality, Belief in work. | |

I HEREBY DECLARE THAT THE INFORMATION GIVEN ABOVE IS TRUE TO THE BEST OF MY KNOWLEDGE.

PLACE -

DATE -

Yours Faithfully

(Panchal Dnyaneshwar Anantrao)